{
    "subject": "resource/International_Airlines_Group",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Spain",
    "human_readable": "The location of International Airlines Group is Spain.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9691917896270752,
            "question": "Is International Airlines Group based in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.966677725315094,
            "question": "Can we find International Airlines Group in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8358452916145325,
            "question": "Where is the International Airlines Group located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6901259422302246,
            "question": "What is the geographical location of International Airlines Group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6636834144592285,
            "question": "What is the headquarters location of International Airlines Group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5998870134353638,
            "question": "Where are the main offices of International Airlines Group situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.474662721157074,
            "question": "To which country does International Airlines Group belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42657390236854553,
            "question": "In what country does International Airlines Group operate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34462764859199524,
            "question": "What is the home country of International Airlines Group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26976561546325684,
            "question": "Which nation houses International Airlines Group's operations?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The location of International Airlines Group is Spain.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7135_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the home country of International Airlines Group?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7135_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what country does International Airlines Group operate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7135_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does International Airlines Group belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7135_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7135_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7135_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7135_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7135_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7135_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7135_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7135_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7135_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7135_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7135_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents state that IAG is a Spanish registered company, they also clearly indicate that its corporate headquarters is in London, UK.  Therefore, the statement \"The location of International Airlines Group is Spain\" is not entirely accurate based on the provided information. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the query in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: While it is mentioned that IAG has its registered office in Madrid, Spain, and corporate headquarters in London, UK, it is not accurate to say that the location of International Airlines Group is solely Spain. The documents also mention London as a location for the corporate head office."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents indicate that International Airlines Group (IAG) has its registered office in Madrid, Spain, and its corporate headquarters in London, England. While the primary registration is in Spain, the statement \"The location of International Airlines Group is Spain\" can be considered accurate based on the context provided, as Spain is indeed one of the key locations associated with IAG."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "IAG has its registered office in Madrid, Spain, but its operational headquarters are in London, UK. Therefore, it cannot be accurately stated that the location of International Airlines Group is Spain.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple sources state that while IAG is registered in Spain, its corporate headquarters are located in London, UK.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information indicates that the registered office of International Airlines Group (AIG) or International Consolidated Airlines Group S.A. (IAG) is in Madrid, Spain, and its operational/corporate headquarters is in London, UK. This suggests that while Spain is a significant location for IAG, it is not exclusive to being the sole location.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}